# Rebecca Joseph

Hebron IN 46341 | Phone: 219 3084853 | Email: cosette37@hotmail.com

Linkedln: /rebecca-joseph-992b0b169/ | Rebecca Joseph (cosette3737.github.io)

## Summary

Highly motivated, self-directed, and versatile lifelong learner with a strong background in data analysis, data flow, and healthcare; pursuing a role in analysis. Skilled in data wrangling and analysis with tools such as SQL and python, while also bringing a well rounded set of healthcare knowledge from professional experience in a healthcare setting, with a familiarity of teamwork, communication, and problem solving.

#### Technical Skills

SQL, Statistics, Excel, Microsoft Office, Tableau, VBA, Github/Git, API, Social Media Mining, Hadoop, Machine Learning, Flask, Numpy, Pandas, Jupyter Notebook, SciPy, Heroku, Command Line, Python, PostgresQL, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, MetaBase, Microsoft Azure

# **Projects**

**Property Value Prediction** | Properties (property-sales-predictor-2020.herokuapp.com) After collecting and analyzing data from Indiana Stats, a model was created using machine learning to allow property value prediction. Additionally, a dashboard and comp discovery were added to allow further exploration of the data. In order to complete this project, we used the following:

 Python, Flask, API, Machine Learning, Excel, SQLAlchemy, Pandas, Matplotlib, HTML, CSS, JS

#### **ETL** | Cosette3737/ETL-Project (github.com)

For the scope of this project, we were asked to extract, transform, and load several data sets on gun related violence into an SQL database, then perform analysis on the data. In order to complete this project, we used the following:

Python, Jupyter Notebook, Pandas, Sqlalchemy, Matplotlib

## Covid Dashboard | covid-states-2020.herokuapp.com

This project examines the spread of covid in an interactive dashboard. The following tools were utilized for the project:

 Python, Visual Studio, HTML, JS CSS, D3, Google Charts, Plotly, Flask, API, Heroku, Postgress, Pandas.

# Experience

# Radiation Therapist | SkinCure Oncology

2017-Current | Chicago, IL

- Held key role communicating between national and billing team and 3rd parties.
- Act as lead implementation expert for startup of new department
- Management of patient schedules, department supplies, film badge reports
- Created comprehensive documentation of best practices and procedures
- Establish and maintenance of Radiation Protection Program and Quality Assurance
- Perform daily imaging and treatment and maintain treatment and imaging records
- Maintain a 99.9% patient satisfaction response survey for 2020.

### Radiation Therapist | Franciscan Health

2016-2017 | Crown Point, IN

- Perform daily treatments and simulation of patients with ionizing radiation.
- Maintain treatment records, quality assurance and patient imaging records.

## Radiation Therapist | Southland Hematology Oncology

2012-2016 | Mokena, IL

- Perform daily treatments and simulation of patients with ionizing radiation.
- Maintain treatment records
- Quality assurance of equipment and patient imaging.
- Train student therapists within the organization

## Radiation Therapist | Hoffman Cancer Center

2005-2012 | Joliet, IL

- Perform daily treatments and simulation of patients with ionizing radiation.
- Maintain treatment records.
- Quality assurance of equipment and patient imaging.
- Train student therapists within the organization

### Education

Boot Camp of Data Analytics Certificate

Butler University | 2021

Bachelor of Science: Medical Imaging Technology Indiana University | 2018

Associates Degree: Radiologic Sciences Indiana University | 2005